

Edyta Szarowska

JUNIOR FRONTEND DEVELOPER

PERSONAL PROFILE

I have been intensively learning web application programming for three years.

I have eight months of commercial experience in creating and maintaining software. I want to develop my competences in finding new solutions during the current problem solving.

TECH STACK

- -HTML -
- -CSS3/SCSS -
- -JavaScript -
- -ReactJS -
- -Next.js -
- -Git/Github/Gitlab -
- -Bootstrap/Chakra UI/StyleComponent -
- -Redux -
- -Sass -

CONTACT DETAILS

Telephone: +48 666 886 255

Email: edyta.szarowska.dev@gmail.com

Portfolio: http://edyta-szarowska-

portfolio.netlify.com/

Github: http://github.com/Edyta2801 LinkedIn: http://linkedin.com/in/edyta-

szarowska/

EXPERIENCE

JAVASCRIPT TREINEE

intive Patronage 2022 | 01.2022 - current

An original internship program consisting in gaining experience in working in IT in teams and creating software from start to finish, using new technologies and tools

FRONTEND DEVELOPMENT MENTEE

Mentoring Dare IT| 11.2021 - current

Mentoring program during which I work with a mentor on the technical skills of Frontend developer and soft skills (time management, giving feedback, teamwork, Agile. Scrum).

JUNIOR FRONTEND DEVELOPER

Innokrea sp. z o.o. | 06.2021 - 08.2021

Work on developing auction applicationj, tech-stack: Next.js, TypeScript,, Redux, Storybook, StyleComponents.

STUDENT IN SZKOŁA REACTA

Szkoła Reacta Patryk Omiotek| 10.2020 -03.2021 Practical use of React, js, Redux oraz Next. js, testing.

WEB DEVELOPER

Agencja Reklamowa Cumulus | 06.2020 - 10.2020

Working mainly with CMS Wordpress, working in the Scrum methodology. I was a project manager for one of the projects.

TRAINEE GRAPHIC DESIGNER

Centrum Szkoleń i Innowacji Sp. z o.o. | 02.2020 - 05.2020 Computer graphics training (ECCC certificate) and internship - practical use of Photoshop and Corel.

BOOTCAMP STUDENTJUNIOR FRONTEND DEVELOPER

InfoShare Academy sp. z o.o. |10.2018 - 12.2018

320 hours of training provided knowledge and practical skills in the field of: JavaScript, REST, JSON, AJAX, React, Redux, HTML5 / CSS, Git. Group project in the Scrum methodology.

PYTHON TRAINING STUDENT

InfoShare Academy sp. z o.o. | 01.2018 - 03.2018

45 hours of training in basic programming knowledge in the field of analytical problem solving and creating Python programs.

SPECIALIST IN MSP/BROKER SALES

PZU SA, Lublin | 11.2007 - 08.2018

QUALITY AUDITOR

RHM Avana Bakeries Newport, Wales | 02.2007 - 07.2007

EDUCATION

KOSZALIN UNIVERSITY OF TECHNOLOGY

Master of Management and Marketing Postgraduate Studies Quality Auditor

LANGUAGES

POLISH- NATIVE LANGUAGE ENGLISH- B2

INTEREST

Personal effectiveness, learning to play the piano